Tell me Sashar ji, today there are many companies, first of all let's take a
look at Jefferies India
Hotels. Jefferies has given its
opinion on India Hotels. Jefferies has a
buy call target of 900. Jefferies believes
that the management has given strong growth
numbers till 53. And there is one more thing in this,
Jefferies has said that they have
achieved their growth in the past, which gives confidence
that they will be successful in achieving the guidance in future as well.
Then there is
HSBC's opinion on UPL. HSBC has given a
buy call target of 680.
They have said that the private equity
investment that has happened in Adventa
is a pleasant surprise, due to which valuations can
also be seen getting a boost. Then
we have some reports from Morgan Stanley.
Morgan Stanley has a report on TCS. There is an
overweight call and the target is
4660. They have said that the management
is indicating that some
strength is being seen, but overall, a
little cautious right now.  The outlook is
regarding the demand environment and the levers
are utilization, employee pyramid and
productivity of improved revenue. Then
if we talk about IIC Lard, there is an
overweight call and the target is 2400. The company
is on track to achieve that. In Q4, the
exit combine ratio guidelines given were
10.5. You can take that. It has also been said
that the regulatory changes that will happen
regarding long term policies in accounting may have an
impact on the company.
Then there is Morgan Stanley's
overweight call on Shriram Finance, in which the
target is 4200. They have said that the
medium term growth which can be seen can be
seen in the range of 15 to 20
and the guidance of 15 for Shriram
Finance will be seen to be maintained.
If we talk about it, they have
given trend based opinion. Morgan Stanley has an
overweight call here also and the target is 8032 in
which quality  And the consistency that they have been
maintaining and this is regarding the new
format that they have been considered like startups.
Overall, look at the
four reports of Morgan Stanley, all four have overweight
calls. The remaining two reports are buy
calls, which means that the foreign brokers who have given so many calls
today, they are mostly seen giving positive overweight or
buy calls. So,
in this distraught market, Shaurya has
brought some good news and that too from
where everyone wants to hear. Jefferies is
calling Indian Hotels for a target of 900.
Indian Hotels is also doing well.
786 has come in this fallen market.
UPL counter is also in the green mark.
HSBC report is buy call
for their target of 680. TCS, the IT
giant, has a target of ₹660 and ISA Luba has a
target of ₹2400. Shriram Finance 4200. Trent
8032. So, most of the stocks are from 2 to
4000-8000, which are small
stocks.  The ones our investors generally
focus on could be UPL or Indian
Hotels. Here the targets are 680 and 900.
So on the buy side, these two calls will be the
highlights of today and you can look at the rest of the counters as per your
portfolio. So,
thank you very much for joining us and
giving us your valuable time and telling us
what is the view of foreign brokerage houses today.
[Music]